Not Without Hope is a mystery, thriller, drama film directed by Joe Carnahan.
A group of friends' fishing boat capsizes off the coast of Mexico and
they're left alone stranded at sea and struggling for survival.
Nick Schuyler, played by Zachary Levi.
Timothy Close, played by Josh Duhamel.
Marquis Cooper, played by Quentin Plair.
Corey Smith, played by Terrence Terrell.
Will Bleakley, played by Marshall Cook.
Marcia, played by JoBeth Williams.
Not Without Hope is a 2025 survival thriller film directed by Joe Carnahan and starring Zachary Levi as Nick Schuyler, the real-life
sole survivor of a 2009 boating accident that took the lives of NFL football players Marquis Cooper and Corey Smith.
The screenplay was written by E.
Nicholas Mariani and Joe Carnahan and is based on Schuyler and Jeré
Longman's 2010 nonfiction book of the same title.
The film premiered at Austin Film Festival on October 25, 2025,
and was released in theaters on December 12.
The film explores themes of sentimental, defiant, tragic.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.